<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dotfiles on chtc&#39;s decaying mental fucked-up technology state</title>
    <link>https://chtc.neocities.org/tag/dotfiles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dotfiles on chtc&#39;s decaying mental fucked-up technology state</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021, chtc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chtc.neocities.org/tag/dotfiles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dotfiles</title>
      <link>https://chtc.neocities.org/dotfiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chtc.neocities.org/dotfiles/</guid>
      <description>These are my awesome (actually horrible) dotfiles.
Screenshots are located in the imgs folder and shown in README’s.
This is a web version of the README. Go to the dotfiles repository for more things.
Caution: Changing stuff to make it work/fit your needsYou probably will and must change something in my dotfiles.
I recommend looking through these dotfiles and changing things to fit your setup and/or needs if you want to use this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stuff</title>
      <link>https://chtc.neocities.org/tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chtc.neocities.org/tech/</guid>
      <description>A list of technology related stuff used by me.
Table Of ContentsHello there!Stuff I UseThe ComputerPrograms And StuffHow It LooksStuff That This Site Uses Stuff I UseThe ComputerActually it’s a laptop not a cumputer.
It’s a HP 250 G4 I think.
 Programs And StuffThingWhat it does?OSVoid LinuxBrowserFirefoxTerminalAlacrittyEditorNeovimMusic PlayerNcmpcppWindow ManagerAwesomeShellZshImage ViewerSxivPDF ViewerZathura How It LooksThere are screenshots in my dotfiles.
 Stuff That This Site UsesThingWhat it does?GitLabHosting original and built files and pushing to neocitiesNeocitiesHostingHugoBuilding the siteHugo Bearblog (modified version)ThemeAsciidoctorPages are written in this and converted to HTML </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
