<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dank Web Presence on chtc&#39;s decaying mental fucked-up technology state</title>
    <link>https://chtc.neocities.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dank Web Presence on chtc&#39;s decaying mental fucked-up technology state</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021, chtc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 17:26:03 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chtc.neocities.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How 2 Do Someones Mom 101</title>
      <link>https://chtc.neocities.org/blog/how-2-do-someones-mom-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 17:26:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chtc.neocities.org/blog/how-2-do-someones-mom-101/</guid>
      <description>Welcum! In this post I will teach you how to do someones mom!
Table Of Contentsi did ur mom before u even laid eyes on this postWhat 2 DoWhat 2 do if the mom did you?Tips &amp;#39;n Tricks What 2 DoGo to their houseEnter bedroomWait for momma in bedroomDo their mother What 2 do if the mom did you?Deal with it.
 Tips &amp;#39;n TricksUse sexiarzLearn how 2 do it by watching secks godz like johny sin and xXx_PussySlayer666_xXx </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dotfiles</title>
      <link>https://chtc.neocities.org/dotfiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chtc.neocities.org/dotfiles/</guid>
      <description>These are my awesome (actually horrible) dotfiles.
Screenshots are located in the imgs folder and shown in README’s.
This is a web version of the README. Go to the dotfiles repository for more things.
Caution: Changing stuff to make it work/fit your needsYou probably will and must change something in my dotfiles.
I recommend looking through these dotfiles and changing things to fit your setup and/or needs if you want to use this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Stuff</title>
      <link>https://chtc.neocities.org/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chtc.neocities.org/media/</guid>
      <description>List of media that I am currently consuming/planning to consume/consumed.
Everything is sorted alphabetically and are ordered by status like this: Watching/Playing -&amp;gt; Infinitely Playing (games only) -&amp;gt; On Hold -&amp;gt; Plan To Watch/Play -&amp;gt; Completed.
Table Of ContentsHello there!MoviesShowsGames MoviesMovieStatusMachine GirlPlan To WatchGinger SnapsPlan To WatchGinger Snaps 2: UnleashedPlan To WatchExteCompletedIncredibles, TheCompletedIncredibles 2, TheCompletedScooby-Doo 2CompletedSharknado 2[1]Completed ShowsShowEpisodeSeasonStatusAggretsuko2/10,10/10[2]3WatchingMr. RobotPlan To WatchAggretsuko2/3CompletedInvincible1/1CompletedLove Death and Robots2/2Completed GamesGameStatusElder Scrolls V: Skyrim, ThePlayingMinecraftInfinitely Playing[3]OpenTTDInfinitely Playing[3]Borderlands: The Pre-SequelOn HoldCelesteOn HoldCry Of FearOn HoldElder Scrolls III: Morrowind, TheOn HoldSuper Meat BoyOn HoldBlood: Fresh SupplyPlan To PlayBorderlandsPlan To PlayBorderlands 3Plan To PlayDoom (2016)Plan To PlayDoom EternalPlan To PlayDUSKPlan To PlayElder Scrolls IV: Oblivion, ThePlan To PlayInjustice: Gods Among Us Ultimate EditionPlan To PlayMetro: 2033 ReduxPlan To PlayMortal Kombat XPlan To PlayMortal Kombat 11Plan To PlayNinja Gaiden SigmaPlan To PlayNinja Gaiden (Sigma) 2Plan To PlayNinja Gaiden 3 Razors EdgePlan To PlayOutlast Whistleblower DLCPlan To PlayPortalPlan To PlayPortal 2Plan To PlayPostal 2Plan To PlayULTRAKILLPlan To PlayBeyond Good And EvilCompletedBorderlands 2CompletedHacknetCompletedHelltaker[4]CompletedJames Bond 007: Blood StoneCompletedLEGO® Movie - Videogame, TheCompletedMetro: Last Light ReduxCompletedMortal Kombat (2009)CompletedNinja Gaiden BlackCompletedOutlastCompletedShadow Warrior 2CompletedTomb Raider (2013)CompletedWalking Dead, TheCompletedWatch DogsCompletedIt was shown on TV and there wasn’t anything interesting playing I think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stuff</title>
      <link>https://chtc.neocities.org/tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chtc.neocities.org/tech/</guid>
      <description>A list of technology related stuff used by me.
Table Of ContentsHello there!Stuff I UseThe ComputerPrograms And StuffHow It LooksStuff That This Site Uses Stuff I UseThe ComputerActually it’s a laptop not a cumputer.
It’s a HP 250 G4 I think.
 Programs And StuffThingWhat it does?OSVoid LinuxBrowserFirefoxTerminalAlacrittyEditorNeovimMusic PlayerNcmpcppWindow ManagerAwesomeShellZshImage ViewerSxivPDF ViewerZathura How It LooksThere are screenshots in my dotfiles.
 Stuff That This Site UsesThingWhat it does?GitLabHosting original and built files and pushing to neocitiesNeocitiesHostingHugoBuilding the siteHugo Bearblog (modified version)ThemeAsciidoctorPages are written in this and converted to HTML </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
