<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>shows on chtc&#39;s decaying mental state</title>
    <link>https://chtc.neocities.org/tag/shows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in shows on chtc&#39;s decaying mental state</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021, chtc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chtc.neocities.org/tag/shows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Media List</title>
      <link>https://chtc.neocities.org/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chtc.neocities.org/media/</guid>
      <description>List of media that I am currently consuming/planning to consume/consumed.
Everything is sorted alphabetically and are ordered by status like this: Watching/Playing -&amp;gt; Infinitely Playing (games only) -&amp;gt; On Hold -&amp;gt; Plan To Watch/Play -&amp;gt; Completed.
Table Of ContentsHello there!MoviesShowsGames MoviesMovieStatusMachine GirlPlan To WatchGinger SnapsPlan To WatchGinger Snaps 2: UnleashedPlan To WatchExteCompletedIncredibles, TheCompletedIncredibles 2, TheCompletedScooby-Doo 2CompletedSharknado 2[1]Completed ShowsShowEpisodeSeasonStatusAggretsuko2/10,10/10[2]3WatchingMr. RobotPlan To WatchAggretsuko2/3CompletedInvincible1/1CompletedLove Death and Robots2/2Completed GamesGameStatusElder Scrolls V: Skyrim, ThePlayingMinecraftInfinitely Playing[3]OpenTTDInfinitely Playing[3]Borderlands: The Pre-SequelOn HoldCelesteOn HoldCry Of FearOn HoldElder Scrolls III: Morrowind, TheOn HoldSuper Meat BoyOn HoldBlood: Fresh SupplyPlan To PlayBorderlandsPlan To PlayBorderlands 3Plan To PlayDoom (2016)Plan To PlayDoom EternalPlan To PlayDUSKPlan To PlayElder Scrolls IV: Oblivion, ThePlan To PlayInjustice: Gods Among Us Ultimate EditionPlan To PlayMetro: 2033 ReduxPlan To PlayMortal Kombat XPlan To PlayMortal Kombat 11Plan To PlayNinja Gaiden SigmaPlan To PlayNinja Gaiden (Sigma) 2Plan To PlayNinja Gaiden 3 Razors EdgePlan To PlayOutlast Whistleblower DLCPlan To PlayPortalPlan To PlayPortal 2Plan To PlayPostal 2Plan To PlayULTRAKILLPlan To PlayBeyond Good And EvilCompletedBorderlands 2CompletedHacknetCompletedHelltaker[4]CompletedJames Bond 007: Blood StoneCompletedLEGO® Movie - Videogame, TheCompletedMetro: Last Light ReduxCompletedMortal Kombat (2009)CompletedNinja Gaiden BlackCompletedOutlastCompletedShadow Warrior 2CompletedTomb Raider (2013)CompletedWalking Dead, TheCompletedWatch DogsCompletedIt was shown on TV and there wasn’t anything interesting playing I think.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
